let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What’s the name of Meatloaf’s character in The Rocky Horror Picture Show?",
    answer: "Eddie",
    options: [
      "Eddie",
      "Henry",
      "Chuck",
      "Al"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who actually drew the sketch of Rose in Titanic?",
    answer: "James Cameron",
    options: [
      "Leonardo DiCaprio",
      "Billy Zane",
      "James Cameron",
      "Kathy Bates"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who voices Joy in Pixar’s Inside Out?",
    answer: "Amy Poehler",
    options: [
      "Tina Fey",
      "Kathryn Hahn",
      "Ellen DeGeneres",
      "Amy Poehler"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Where were The Lord of the Rings movies filmed?",
    answer: "New Zealand",
    options: [
      "Ireland",
      "Iceland",
      "New Zealand",
      "Australia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which country does Forrest Gump travel to as part of the All-American Ping-Pong Team?",
    answer: "China",
    options: [
      "Vietnam",
      "China",
      "Sweden",
      "France"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which actor was in the following movies: The Outsiders, Wayne’s World and Tommy Boy?",
    answer: "C.Thomas Howell",
    options: [
      "Tom Cruise",
      "Matt Dillon",
      "Rob Lowe",
      "C.Thomas Howell"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who was the first Black person to win an Oscar?",
    answer: "Hattie McDaniel",
    options: [
      "Hattie McDaniel",
      "Sidney Poitier",
      "Dorothy Dandridge",
      "James Earl Jones"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which is not the name of a child selected to tour the Wonka factory in Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory?",
    answer: "Billy Warp",
    options: [
      "Billy Warp",
      "Veruca Salt",
      "Mike Teavee",
      "Charlie Bucket"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Freddy Krueger wears a striped sweater that is which colors?",
    answer: "Red and green",
    options: [
      "Red and blue",
      "Orange and green",
      "Red and green",
      "Orange and brown"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the name of the fictional land where Frozen takes place?",
    answer: "Arendelle",
    options: [
      "Arendelle",
      "Naples",
      "Florin",
      "Grimm"
    ]
  },
];

